<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Pages on ObjShadow&#39;s Blog</title>
        <link>//localhost:1313/en/page/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Pages on ObjShadow&#39;s Blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/en/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>About</title>
        <link>//localhost:1313/en/page/about/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>//localhost:1313/en/page/about/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;font size=5&gt;Use the most common and easy-to-understand language to write the most hardcore anti-censorship technical content. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the slogan of this blog, and it is also the goal, purpose, and original intention of the blog. &lt;br&gt;
Writing these technical contents is to hope that readers can understand the spirit of freedom and human ethics behind anti-censorship,&lt;br&gt;
and also be able to gain insight into the technical principles behind anti-censorship, understand cutting-edge anti-censorship research,&lt;br&gt;
and be able to defend their own information freedom, privacy security, and personal dignity in the digital space. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main direction of this blog is to analyze the circumvention tools that are currently in practical use,&lt;br&gt;
and popularize some basic anti-censorship technical principles to readers in an easy-to-understand way,&lt;br&gt;
and follow up on large-scale anti-censorship conferences of academic nature such as &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://foci.community/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;FOCI&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.usenix.org/conference/usenixsecurity24&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;USENIX Security&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;br&gt;
try to provide readers with the most understandable, practical, and cutting-edge anti-censorship technical content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, &lt;br&gt;
I hope that the readers who are reading this article, &lt;br&gt;
will one day break free from this iron cage, &lt;br&gt;
witness that there is no more censorship and totalitarianism in this world, &lt;br&gt;
witness that this blog is no longer necessary, &lt;br&gt;
in the glory of freedom, always remember those &lt;br&gt;
researchers, developers, and propagandists who have contributed to anti-censorship, &lt;br&gt;
and the ordinary people who have tried their best to pursue freedom.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Archives</title>
        <link>//localhost:1313/en/page/archives/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>//localhost:1313/en/page/archives/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Links</title>
        <link>//localhost:1313/en/page/links/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>//localhost:1313/en/page/links/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;欢迎互换友链!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;请在评论区留下你的常用邮箱和网站主页地址。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Search</title>
        <link>//localhost:1313/en/page/search/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>//localhost:1313/en/page/search/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
